A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-9
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-10
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-11
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-12
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-13
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-14
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, north elevation, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-15
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, south elevation, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-16
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-17
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-18
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-19
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-20
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-21
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-22
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-23
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-24
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-25
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-26
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-27
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-28
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-29
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-30
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-31
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-32
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-33
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-34
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-35
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-36
- Dranesville Tavern, aerial view, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-37
- Dranesville Tavern, unidentified couple, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-38
- Dranesville Tavern, c. 1935 Virginia State Library photo, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-39
- Dranesville Tavern, original site, 1966; Box 1: DRAN-T-40
- Dranesville Tavern (photo by E. Breitenbach), c. 1967; Box 1: DRAN-T-41
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-42
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-43
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-44
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-45
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-46
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-47
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-48
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-49
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-50
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-51
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-52
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-53
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-54
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-55
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-56
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-57
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-58
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-59
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-60
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-61
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-62
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-63
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-64
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-65
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-66
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-67
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-68
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-69
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-70
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-71
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-72
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-73
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-74
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-75
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-76
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-77
- Dranesville Tavern, end chimney, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-78
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-79
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-80
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-81
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-82
- Dranesville Tavern, east wall, first floor, Cabin A, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-83
- Dranesville Tavern, detail mantel Cabin A, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-84
- Dranesville Tavern, mantel, Cabin B, second floor, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-85
- Dranesville Tavern, fireplace, west wall of south side room, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-86
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-87
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-88
- Dranesville Tavern, kitchen shelf showing attachment to log walls, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-89
- Dranesville Tavern, kitchen wing stairs to half attic, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-90
- Dranesville Tavern, stairs up to porch, closed in, south side, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-91
- Dranesville Tavern, door, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-92
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-93
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-94
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-95
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-96
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-97
- Dranesville Tavern, exploring trap door above "dog trot" area, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-98
- Dranesville Tavern, shelving in old bar room store, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-99
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-100
- Dranesville Tavern, southwest side after porch removal, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-101
- Dranesville Tavern, southwest side after porch removal, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-102
- Dranesville Tavern, southwest side log detail, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-103
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-104
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-105
- Dranesville Tavern, southwest side, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-106
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-107
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-108
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-109
- Dranesville Tavern, partial basement, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-110
- Dranesville Tavern, partial basement, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-111
- Dranesville Tavern, partial basement, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-112
- Dranesville Tavern, lath and plaster, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-113
- Dranesville Tavern, lath and plaster, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-114
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-115
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-116
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-117
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-118
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-119
- Dranesville Tavern, southeast corner Cabin B, butted wall enclosing dog trot, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-120
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-121
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-122
- Dranesville Tavern, chimney base, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-123
- Dranesville Tavern, end chimney, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-124
- Dranesville Tavern, stone end chimney, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-125
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-126
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-127
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-128
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-129
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-130
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-131
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-132
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-133
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-134
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-135
- Dranesville Tavern (c. 1936), Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-136
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-137
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-138
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-139
- Dranesville Tavern, east wall, interior corner, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-140
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-141
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-142
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-143
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-144
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-145
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-146
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-147
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-148
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-149
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-150
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-151
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-152
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-153
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-154
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-155
- Dranesville Tavern, reused beams raised attic over kitchen wing, 1968 March; Box 1: DRAN-T-156
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-157
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-158
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-159
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-160
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-161
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-162
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-163
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-164
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-165
- Dranesville Tavern, N.E. corner Cabin A, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-166
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-167
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-168
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-169
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-170
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-171
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-172
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-173
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-174
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-175
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-176
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-177
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-178
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-179
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-180
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-181
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-182
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-183
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-184
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-185
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-186
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-187
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-188
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-189
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-190
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-191
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-192
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-193
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-194
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-195
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-196
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-197
- Dranesville Tavern, cedar tree in rear, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-198
- Dranesville Tavern, cedar tree in rear, 1968 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-199
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-200
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-201
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-202
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-203
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-204
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-205
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-206
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-207
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-208
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-209
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-210
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-211
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-212
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-213
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-214
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-215
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-216
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-217
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-218
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-219
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-220
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-221
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-222
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-223
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-224
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-225
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-226
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-227
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-228
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-229
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-230
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-231
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-232
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-233
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-234
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-235
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-236
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-237
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-238
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-239
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-240
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-241
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-242
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-243
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-244
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-245
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-246
- Dranesville Tavern, lab crew at work, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-247
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-248
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-249
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-250
- Dranesville Tavern, excavation of latrine in garden area, looking north, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-251
- Dranesville Tavern, garden trenches, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-252
- Dranesville Tavern, highway department scalping of west pasture and looking for barn foundations, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-253
- Dranesville Tavern, foundations of old barn?, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-254
- Dranesville Tavern, ice house excavation, looking west, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-255
- Dranesville Tavern, ice house excavation, looking west, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-256
- Dranesville Tavern, ice house, north wall, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-257
- Dranesville Tavern, Tony Wrenn conferring with Rev. Peterson, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-258
- Dranesville Tavern, bags inside house for storage, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-259
- Dranesville Tavern, garden trench, no latrine evidences, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-260
- Dranesville Tavern, lunch hour at the dig, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-261
- Dranesville Tavern, garden trenches looking east, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-262
- Dranesville Tavern, looking for foundations of log barn complex, looking south, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-263
- Dranesville Tavern, lab work, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-264
- Dranesville Tavern, screening dirt from cellar, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-265
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 June; Box 1: DRAN-T-267
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-268
- Dranesville Tavern, prior to moving (photo by Nan Netherton), 1968 September; Box 1: DRAN-T-269
- Dranesville Tavern, windows boarded for movement, 1968 April; Box 1: DRAN-T-270
- Dranesville Tavern, stone end chimney, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-271
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 May; Box 1: DRAN-T-272
- Dranesville Tavern, 1968 September; Box 1: DRAN-T-273
- Dranesville Tavern, moving, 1968 September; Box 1: DRAN-T-274
- Dranesville Tavern (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973 February; Box 1: DRAN-T-275
- Dranesville Tavern (photo by FCPA), 1975; Box 1: DRAN-T-276
- Dranesville Tavern, Undated; Box 1: DRAN-T-277
- Drover's Rest, McLean, VA (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 1: DROV-1
- Eglin House, McLean, VA (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: EGLI-1 (1 of 2)
- Eglin House, McLean, VA (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: EGLI-1 (2 of 2)
- Eglin House, McLean, VA, c. 1972; Box 2: EGLI-2 (1 of 2)
- Eglin House, McLean, VA, c. 1972; Box 2: EGLI-2 (2 of 2)
- Eglin House, McLean, VA (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 2: EGLI-3
- Fairfax Arms, Lorton, VA, 1968 May; Box 2: FX-AR-1
- Fairview Farms, 1968 May; Box 2: FAIR-V-1
- Fairview Farms, 1968 May; Box 2: FAIR-V-2
- Fairview Farms, 1968 May; Box 2: FAIR-V-3
- Fairview Farms, 1968 May; Box 2: FAIR-V-4
- Falls Church (city), aerial view, Undated; Box 2: FALL-1
- The Falls Church, interior 1913-1943 (photo by Herb Hunter), Undated; Box 2: FALL-FC-1
- The Falls Church, 1972-1977 Lee Highway sign, Undated; Box 2: FALL-FC-2
- The Falls Church, interior, Advent, 1975; Box 2: FALL-FC-4
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA, view of bunker, 1976; Box 2: FREE-1
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA (photo by FCPA), 1976; Box 2: FREE-2
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA, 1968; Box 2: FREE-3
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA, 1968; Box 2: FREE-4
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA, 1968; Box 2: FREE-5
- Freedom Hill Fort, Vienna, VA, 1968; Box 2: FREE-6
- Frying Pan Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FRYP-CH-1 (1 of 3)
- Frying Pan Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FRYP-CH-1 (2 of 3)
- Frying Pan Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FRYP-CH-1 (3 of 3)
- Frying Pan Church, 1968 March; Box 2: FRYP-CH-3
- Frying Pan Church, 1968 March; Box 2: FRYP-CH-4
- Frying Pan Farm Park, Milk Separator Shed, Undated; Box 2: FRYP-FP-2
- North Branch Potomac at Wilson, down stream, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-1
- North Branch Potomac at Wilson, up stream, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-2
- Marsh east of Fairfax Stone Road - side park, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-3
- Trail to Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-4
- Pipeline enroute to Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-5
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-6
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-7
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-8
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-9
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-10
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-11
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-12
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-13
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-14
- At Fairfax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-15
- Faifrax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-16
- Faifrax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-17
- Faifrax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-18
- Faifrax Stone, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-19
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-20
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-21
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-22
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-23
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-24
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-25
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-26
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-27
- Kempton, Maryland, 1970 August 22; Box 2: FX-STONE-28
- County Personnel Office, 4101 Chain Bridge Road, vacated in 1985, 1983 October; Box 2: FXCI-A-1
- County Personnel Office, 4101 Chain Bridge Road, close up of sign, 1980 February; Box 2: FXCI-A-2
- Barbour House, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BARB-1
- Barbour House, Fairfax City (photo by Steve Behrens), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BARB-2
- Barbour House, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BARB-3
- Blenheim, Fairfax City (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-1 (1 of 2)
- Blenheim, Fairfax City (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-1 (2 of 2)
- Blenheim, Fairfax City, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-3
- Blenheim, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-4
- Blenheim, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-5
- Blenheim, Fairfax City, Attic Walls, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-6
- Blenheim, Fairfax City (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-BLEN-7
- City Hall, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-CITY-H-1
- City Seal on automobile, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-CITY-S-1
- Confederate Monument, Fairfax Cemetery, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-CONF-1
- D'Astra Tenement (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FXCI-DAST-1
- Draper House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-DRAP-1
- Draper House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-DRAP-2 (1 of 2)
- Draper House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-DRAP-2 (2 of 2)
- Draper House, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-DRAP-3
- Draper House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-DRAP-4
- Earp's Ordinary, 1961; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-1
- Earp's Ordinary (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-2 (1 of 2)
- Earp's Ordinary (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-2 (2 of 2)
- Earp's Ordinary and Old Town Hall next door, 1968; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-4
- Earp's Ordinary, Main Room, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-5
- Earp's Ordinary, Sitting Room, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-6
- Earp's Ordinary, Hallway, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-7
- Earp's Ordinary, Stairway, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-8
- Earp's Ordinary, Bedroom, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-9
- Earp's Ordinary, circa 1870s shot, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-EARP-10
- Fairfax Hay and Grain, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FXHA-1
- Five Chimneys, 1966; Box 2: FXCI-FIVE-1 (1 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, 1966; Box 2: FXCI-FIVE-1 (2 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FIVE-2
- Five Chimneys, close up, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FIVE-3
- Five Chimneys, chimney, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FIVE-4
- Ford Building, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FORD-1
- Ford Building, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FORD-2
- The Ford Carriage House, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FORD-CA-1
- Fairfax Herald Building, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-FXHE-1
- Fairfax Herald Building, Old Printing Press, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-HXHE-2
- High Offley, site of Massey Building (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FXCI-HIGH-1 (1 OF 2)
- High Offley, site of Massey Building (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FXCI-HIGH-1 (2 OF 2)
- High Offley, site of Massey Building (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 2: FXCI-HIGH-2
- McCandlish House, Conrad Bower, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-MCCA-1
- McCandlish House, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-MCCA-2
- Main Street, Fairfax City, circa 1903, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-MAIN-1
- Main Street, Fairfax City, 1975; Box 2: FXCI-MAIN-2
- Mosby capturing Stoughton (illustration), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-MOSB-CA-1
- Mosby Marker, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-MOSB-MA-1
- National Bank of Fairfax, 1963; Box 2: FXCI-NATI-1
- Oliver House, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-OLIV-1
- Fairfax City Post Office, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-POST-1
- Judge Thomas tenement, porch posts from courthouse, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-THOM-1
- Old Town Hall (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-TOWN-1 (1 OF 2)
- Old Town Hall (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-TOWN-1 (2 OF 2)
- Old Town Hall (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TOWN-2
- Old Town Hall (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 2: FXCI-TOWN-3
- Truro Chapel, Fairfax City (photo by Steve Behrens), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-1
- Truro Chapel, Fairfax City (photo by Steve Behrens), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-2 (1 OF 2)
- Truro Chapel, Fairfax City (photo by Steve Behrens), 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-2 (2 OF 2)
- Truro Chapel with Mosby Monument, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-3
- Truro Episcopal Church, 1974 May; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-4
- Truro Episcopal Church, 1974 May; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-5 (1 OF 3)
- Truro Episcopal Church, 1974 May; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-5 (2 OF 3)
- Truro Episcopal Church, 1974 May; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-5 (3 OF 3)
- Truro Rectory, Gunnell House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-6 (1 OF 2)
- Truro Rectory, Gunnell House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-6 (1 OF 2)
- Truro Rectory, 1971; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-7
- Truro Rectory, 1976; Box 2: FXCI-TRUR-8
- Indian burning fields, poison fields, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-1 (1 OF 2)